呜~
Whoo!
翻译：果果
翻译：谢大牌
翻译：夏末
贝城亡命之徒
翻译：Garfield
翻译：叨叨
开门!
Open up!
校对：小已
是自己人 老兄
It's your dog, bro!
校对：Riki
我们受委托来找一个叫
We've got a warrant for
Hector De la Taco的人
a Hector De la Taco.
让他出来吧
So send him on out.
校对：Shmily
你们找错房子 也找错人了
You've got the wrong house, ese.
为什么要替我们担心里面没有什么呢
Why don't you let me worry about that there's nothing?
后期：小白
我们是FBI!
This is the FBI! Why the
你他妈怎么还不开门 走吧
fuck don't you open the fucking door? Let's go!
真聪明 听着 贱人们
That's cute. Look! You putas
给你们十秒钟 给我滚蛋
got ten seconds to get the fuck off my stoop!
- 怎么样?   - 贱人们?
- OK? - Putas?
嘿 老弟 你知道么 我们走错了
Hey, man! You know what, man? We got off to the wrong foot!
你他妈没走错 快滚吧
You're damn fucking right we did!
后期：十一
好吧 伙计 后退一步
All right, man! Just take a step back
再看一眼我们的授权证明
and take another look at our credentials!
后期：迷毁
McQueen警官
Officer McQueen, would you
能麻烦您给那个好小伙看看您的徽章么
please show this nice young gentleman your badge?
什么都看不见
I can't see shit!
呜!
Whoo!
你不需要它了
You ain't gonna need this no more.
消停点! 好好学学怎么说话
Stop it! If you had bothered to learn the language,
你知道你可以对我说什么吗
you know what you could be saying to me right now?
你知道你能说什么吗
Do you know what you could be saying?
你可以说,"嘿 老兄
You could be saying, "Hey, man,
这是个天大的误会
this is a big mistake.
我是联邦警察 我还有妻子
I'm a Federale. I've got a wife!
我的妻儿还在家里 求你不要杀我"
I got a wife and I got a kid at home! Please don't let me die!"
但这是你想做的 说这些没用的废话
But that's all you want to do! Talk in your jibber-jabber.
这荒谬得就像是
That would be like me going
在墨西哥希望每个人都说英语一样
to Mexico and expect everybody to speak American.
全能的主啊! 我是说 我该怎么办...
God Almighty! I mean, what am I...?
你告诉我我该怎么办 我应该干嘛?
You tell me what I'm supposed to do. What am I supposed to do?
没错 你有工作
All right, you've got a job.
对吧? 你清理厕所 你割草
Right? You clean toilets, or cut grass,
你干什么都行 而我的工作
or whatever the hell it is you do. This is what I do.
是爆头 懂吗
I shoot people in the face. You understand?
有人希望你永远地离开
Somebody wanted you gone,
你知道他们是冲谁来的 就是在这的那个家伙
you know who they came to. This guy right here.
明白了吧 抱歉 但如你所知
You know? So I'm sorry. But just so you know,
这无关个人 好吗
this ain't nothing personal. All right?
你不会相信的
You ain't gonna believe this.
什么
Yeah?
我们真的找错了
We got the wrong house.
这破事要怎么解决
Oh, this shit ain't gonna turn out well!
没听见吗
You don't listen, man!
你就不靠谱得像百战天虫一样 该死!
You're like MacGruber! Goddamnit, man!
可不是么
Well, ain't that some shit.
- 警长   - 怎么回事
- Sheriff? - What's the story?
一个不留的大屠杀
It's just an all-out massacre.
十三具尸体 一堆堆的毒品
Thirteen dead bodies, mounds of drugs,
枪支 唾液还有混球 一团糟
guns, spit and ass. It's a mess.
什么人干的?
So who were these miscreants?
没人有什么可疑的地方
No one appeared to be anybody special.
只有几个普通的店家和几辆破车
Just run-of-the-mill dealers and bangers.
- 有证人吗   - 呃 你知道的
- Anybody talking? - Ah, you know how it is.
什么也没听见 什么也没看见
Nobody heard nothing, nobody saw nothing,
没人跟警察说话
and nobody talks to the po-po.
好吧 这听起来倒像那么回事
Yeah, that sounds about right.
写好必要的文件
Fill out all the necessary paperwork,
把尸体运走
run the bodies through the county.
报告放我桌上
Have the report on my desk.
长官 恕我擅自行动
Sir, I also took the liberty
继续查案以解决事件去了
to go ahead and put it out over the wire.
看看我们能不能揪出凶手
See if we can get a bead on these shooters.
为什么要这样做
Now, why would you go and do that?
加快案件的审理啊
Trying to speed things along.
哟
Oh!
你是说我的工作做不好咯
You think I can't do my job.
我只是想...
I just thought...
不要自作主张 什么都别做!
Don't do that! Don't ever do that.
就照我说的做
Just do as you're told.
- 什么事都没有?   - 是的!
- Nothing? - Nope!
- 一点都没追究?   - 嗯哼
- Not even half? - Mm-mm.
这不太对! 豁出了老命却一毛钱都拿不到
Something's gotta change! Risking our necks for no money.
胡说
This some bullshit!
这样的日子我已经厌烦了
I'm about tired of us getting
每天都在折腾却一无所获 听见没
fucked six ways from Sunday, you hear me?
该死
Goddang, man!
我本来想泡在钱堆里的
I was gonna put a pool in with that money.
该死 混账东西
Goddang, motherfucker!
别吵了 走开 狗娘养的
Stop! Yeah, walk away, bitch!
小子 你该庆幸我现在没心情抽你屁股吧！
You lucky I ain't in the mood to whip your ass, boy!
又浪费粮食 混账
Wasting food, motherfucker.
- 需要帮忙吗?   - 噢 见鬼
- Can I help you? - Oh, shit!
- 抱歉 你吓到我了   - 效果不错
- Sorry. You scared me. - That's what I do.
我是Celeste
I'm Celeste.
我想跟你和你的朋友们谈谈
I was hoping to talk to you and your friends.
朋友们? 我可没什么朋友
Friends? I ain't got no friends.
只有一帮兄弟
I've got my brothers.
房子 车
Got my house. My car.
还有在我面前的面前迷人的小Chica
I've got a sexy little chica standing in front of me.
可我没朋友
But I ain't got no friends.
你想做我朋友吗
You wanna be my friend?
今天早上的事我都看见了
I saw you this morning.
我想让你们也帮我做点事情
I was hoping to acquire your services.
那你找错人了 今天早上我们在教堂
You got the wrong fellas. We was at church this morning.
- 是吗   - 没错
- Really? - Yeah.
所以今天早上在Bacon街横扫整幢房子的
So there's just three other white boys that looked just like you
那三个白人小子只是长得像你们咯
that ripped up a whole house on Bacon Street?
好好想想 怎么多的证人
Trying to figure out how you
你们要怎么走出这个地方
guys walked out of there with all those witnesses.
还有那么多的警察 你们应付得来么
And every cop in the state isn't lined up at your door.
那么 你这么漂亮的女孩
So, what's a pretty little
在那么乱的街区去又是有何贵干呢
girl like you doing in a neighbourhood like that?
我是想去雇个壮汉...
Well, I was there to hire muscle...
雇他去干嘛
Hire him to do what?
从我前夫那要回我的儿子
Get my godson back from my ex-husband.
我先来的
Dibs.
畜生!混账!
Dang it! Cock-blocking motherfucker!
女士 我想你并不清楚你在做什么
Lady, I'm not sure what it is you think you're doing,
但那确实不是我们擅长的方向
but that's not exactly our line of expertise.
- 我付得起钱   - 多少
- I got money. - How much?
一万
Ten thousand.
而且我也觉得救人这种事不太适合我们
Yeah, I don't think saving people is really for us.
你干嘛不把这事交给警察去做呢
You know? Why don't you take that shit to the cops?
他们可不收钱
They'll do it for free.
两万五
Twenty-five thousand.
先付五千
Five thousand up front.
进来见见弟兄们吧
Come on inside and meet the boys.
这就是我要说的 流畅的线条 剖面光滑
This is what I'm talking about. Clean lines, nothing to profile.
也没有那种旋扣器
None of that spinner,
该死的会抬升汽车的液压装置
hydraulic shit to get you lit up.
Sal 我的意思是
What I'm talking about, Sal,
所有东西你都可以用这辆二手的现代索纳塔运
is you transporting anything and everything
这就是原因
in this pre-owned Hyundai Sonata. And here's the reason why.
隐藏的隔间 上面涂有咖啡豆粉和滑石膏
Hidden compartment. Coated with coffee bean and talcum paste
缉毒犬是闻不出来的
no drug dog on the planet Earth can sniff out.
完全不用担心 下个月的这个时候
This space is worry-free, and this time next month,
我要生产出一批这样的车
I'm gonna have a fucking fleet of them.
真是紧
Damn, that's tight.
听见了吗 爸 时间很紧
Hear that, Dad? It's tight.
那么 你们怎么想 弟兄们
So, what do you say, boys?
能帮我跑跑腿吗
You want to take a few road trips for me?
当他妈然啦 Carlos
Abso-fucking-lutely, Carlos.
我们当然不介意当你的骡子
We surely don't mind being your fucking little mule,
Don Carlos
Don Carlos.
我们得讨论讨论分成
But we gotta talk about our cut.
我们总是冒风险的那个
We're the one doing all the risks.
我刚刚想起点事
You know, I just remembered something.
我要电池和厕纸
I need batteries and toilet paper.
我还要那部布拉德皮特的电影
And I need to get that Brad Pitt movie.
大概是他变回婴儿的那部
The one where he turns back into a fucking baby?
没有足够的奶喝 之类的
Running low on milk, a few things.
我想知道我能上哪很方便地弄到
I wonder where I could get
所有的这些东西
all these items in one convenient location?
沃尔玛
Walmart.
沃他妈尔玛 就是这个
Wal-fucking-mart. That's it.
我很喜欢你们这样
I love the way you put
把"他妈"放在每个词里
"Fucking" In the middle of a word like that.
我以后也要这样说话
I'm gonna start using that shit.
你瞧 朋友们 我有点,呃...
You see, guys, I kind of, uh...
看我的未来帝国
...look at my future empire
就像看待沃尔玛的零售犯罪
as the Walmart of bottom-dollar retail crime.
但我们不可能每个人都成为
But, you know, we can't all be
山姆沃尔顿
Sam Walton.
沃尔玛的开办人
那是我的大业
That's my job.
当我的步兵开始谈论像分成
And when my foot soldiers start talking about shit like cuts
诸如此类的鬼话题时
and percentages and things like that,
这可是合伙人的谈话
well, see, that's partner talk.
我需要的不是合伙人
And I don't need a partner.
我要的是装料工 出纳员
I need stockers and cashiers and
雇佣兵 还有苦力们
mercenaries and mules.
想当初 我发现你的时候
And in your case, Padre,
Padre 你只是我在园艺部门碰巧遇到的
dime-bag dealers from the lawn and garden department.
廉价包经营商
Coincidentally, where I found you.
现在呢 Padre 我很喜欢你 真的
Now, Padre, I like you. I really do.
我也喜欢你儿子
I like your son too.
我真的很感激你们父子为我做的那些破事
I really appreciate all the shit you've done for me,
你懂得
you know,
上帝不想看见的那些事
that God wouldn't be proud of.
可是有些事 你还是掐灭苗头
But some things, you just have to stop them before they start.
合作可是野心的祸端
See, partnership leads to ambition.
而野心通向的是一个人们鲜少用到的词语了
Ambition leads to a word they don't use much any more.
叛乱
Mutiny.
- 爸爸 那是什么   - 是坏消息
- Papa, what's that? - It's bad news.
听好了 笨蛋们 这是Celeste
Listen up, dipshits! This here is Celeste.
她要给我们
And she'd like to give us
一大笔钱去把她儿子从她那个游手好闲的前夫
an assload of money to kidnap her godkid back
手里拐回来 这样说对吗
from her deadbeat ex-husband. That about cover it?
- 我想是吧   - 好吧
- I guess so. - Well, OK.
让我先找找这里的失踪人员报导
Let me just find my missing persons report here,
再给你个方案
and I'll get you right set up.
你心思暴露了 老兄
You out your damn mind, brother?
那边的大家伙 是Lincoln
The big fellow over there, that's Lincoln.
说大话的笨蛋是McQueen
The mouthy little faggot here is McQueen.
我是Brick
And I'm Brick.
你跟她提过
Did you happen to mention
绑架不是我们真正的营生吧
that kidnapping ain't exactly what we do?
我早上也在那
I was there this morning.
你在教堂?
You was at church?
当我看见你们几个把整座屋子都
When I saw you guys take out
摆平后毫发无伤地出来时
that whole house and walk out without a scratch,
我就知道你们就是我要找的人
I knew I found my guys.
狗屁 一定有内幕
Bull sheet. What the catch?
是啊 你干嘛不去找警察呢
Yeah. Why didn't you just go to the cops with this?
他小时候喉头被毁坏了 不能说话
His voice box was crushed when he was a kid. He can't talk.
因为我跟她说过我们能做到
'Cause I told her we'd do it.
为什么他要做这么件傻事呢
Why would he go and do a dumb thing like that?
因为你们是我唯一能找到的帮手了
'Cause you guys are my only shot.
我只想要回Rob 带他离开这一切
I just want to get Rob and take him away from all this shit.
周二晚上就没有办法了
That window closes Tuesday night.
我们看起来像联邦快递吗
Do we look like FedEx to you?
- 闭嘴   - 你闭嘴
- Shut up. - You shut up.
- 你才闭嘴   - 你闭嘴
- Shut up, man. - You shut up.
我在跟这位女士说话 闭上你的嘴
I'm talking to the lady. Shut up, man!
- 闭嘴!   - 我只想彻底解脱出来
- Shut up! - I just want peace of mind.
而警察给不了我
That's something the cops can't give me.
- 你觉得我们可以?   - 是的
- And you think we can provide that? - Yeah.
要是他被捕了
If he's arrested,
18个月后他出来然后又找到我
he'll just get out in 18 months and hunt me down.
我们又不是Oodie兄弟公司
This ain't Oodie Brothers Incorporated.
现在是了
It is now.
她给了我们两万五的理由开张
She just gave us 25,000 reasons to open up shop.
预付的五千
Five up front.
弟兄们 这就是我们一直在等的
Guys, it's what we've been waiting for.
这是个机会
It's a chance.
你不是想成为最后一个顾家好男人么
You wanted to be the last true family man,
Clark
Clark.
好吧
Ok.
好吧 女士 你的钱我们收下了
OK, lady. We'll take your money.
我们会把你的孩子弄回来
We'll even get your kid back.
但这个男人 这个 呃
But if this man, this, uh...
Carlos
Carlos.
要是他像你说的这么疯狂
If he's as crazy as you say he is,
他干嘛不一早就杀了你
then why didn't he just kill you in the first place?
他试过
He tried.
所以你们走的时候
So when you leave,
如果Lincoln
it would be great
能爆了他的头那是再好不过了
if Lincoln could put a boot through his skull.
女士们 还有疑问吗
You ladies have any other questions?
Henry 有人在后面等你 办公室里
Henry, there's someone in the back for you. In your office.
谁啊
Who?
Anthony Reese 是ATF的探员
Anthony Reese. He's an ATF agent.
烟酒、火器与爆炸物管理局
- 还很可爱   - 多谢
- Cute, too. - Yeah. Thanks for that.
我进门之前会整理一番的
I'll be sure to freshen up before I go in.
Reese探员
Agent Reese.
我是Henry Millard
Henry Millard.
- 荣幸之至 先生   - 好吧
- Pleasure, sir. - Well...
我们这儿穿正装的可不多见
We don't see suits in here much.
是啊 我想我明白为什么
Yeah, I can see why.
人们怎样能生活在这么热的地方
How do people move in this heat?
我们一直如此
At our own pace.
那么...我能帮你什么呢
So... what can I do you for?
我想问几个问题
Well, I wanted to ask you a few questions regarding the shootout
是关于今天早上的枪战
that occurred earlier today.
我们认为可以确定几个嫌疑人
We think we may have a lead on some suspects.
- 那是真的?   - 是的 先生 没错
- Is that a fact? - Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
这原来...这是个很有意思的地方
It was a... It's an interesting region you have over here.
每隔几个月
It seems every few months
这里都有一大批暴力的罪犯
there's a large number of violent offenders
要么失踪 要么被发现死亡 没有任何征兆
that go missing or show up dead, but there's never any leads.
案件就...那么了断了 真是离奇呢
Cases just... go away. It's very weird.
我觉得现在为杀人犯谋求正义
Well, I guess around here finding justice for murderers
不是当务之急吧
isn't a top priority.
也对 你知道 Oodie兄弟吗
Right. Do you know the Oodie Brothers?
我都知道 孩子
I know all, son. But I
但我能看出你准备好要演说一番啊
can see you came prepared for show and tell.
所以...开始吧
So... get with the getting.
好吧 头号嫌犯!
All right. Prime suspects!
案子始于他们的父亲
Case dating back to their father,
Jonathan Warren Oodie
Jonathan Warren Oodie,
或者Johnny Boy Oodie吧
or Johnny Boy Oodie,
大家这样叫他的
as he was called.
我猜你会很喜欢他
Guessing you would have loved this guy.
显然 在他二十几岁时
Apparently, in his mid-twenties,
Johnny Boy加入了3K党
Johnny Boy got involved with the Klan.
对当时的地方法的执行来说
Made things very colourful
真是添了不少看点
for local law enforcement back in the day.
提前说一句 3K党就要销声匿迹的时候
Flash-forward, KKK just about dumbed themselves out of existence
Johnny Boy
and Johnny Boy
在86年3月的一次联邦毒品突击中
went out in a blaze of glory
带着荣誉死亡了
during a federal drug raid in March of '86.
没人知道孩子的母亲是谁
No known mother to speak of,
他们三个的来历成了圣诞奇迹
which makes these three a Christmas miracle.
听起来熟悉么 Sheriff? 没有吗
Sound familiar to you, Sheriff? No?
没有爷爷奶奶
There were no grandparents
或者亲戚可以适合带孩子的
or kin suitable to take the children in,
所以他们被送到寄养者家里了
so they were sent into foster care.
然后 当他们越来越大时
Then, when they became of age,
他们成为所有人的麻烦了
they started to become everyone's problem
年龄最大的是Brick
The oldest is Brick.
简直就是他父亲的翻版
He is Johnny Boy in the flesh.
似乎天生就无法与麻烦绝缘
Can't seem to stay out of trouble.
而且这小子爱极了他的枪
And boy, does he love his guns.
来他们似乎想试试遵守下法律
Then it looks as though they tried to go legit for a minute.
就把中间那个兄弟
So they put their middle brother,
Lincoln留在了环形拳击场的南方
Lincoln, in Southern Circuit Wrestling.
他最终在拳击场杀了7名男子 你猜怎么着
He ended up killing seven men in the ring. And guess what?
绝对什么都没有了
Absolutely nothing was done about it.
也不是 发起人并没有起诉他
Nope. Promoters wouldn't charge him,
说这只是一场意外
saying it was accidental
而他脖子被扭断的那部分是骗人的玩意
and part of his neck-breaking gimmick.
然后这个人渣从此变得更加捉摸不定
And to make this giant fucker even freakier,
他不能说话了
he cannot talk.
至少上次检查的时候是不能的
Or at least he couldn't last time anybody checked.
那时他正以Dixie Reaper的名号
Wrestled under the name
纵横摔跤界
the Dixie Reaper.
再有就是McQueen  他几乎是文盲
And then there's McQueen. Practically illiterate.
他在内心深处就是个婴儿 他想他自己的方式
He's the baby of the brood. He was well on his way
成为现实中的"特种部队"
to becoming a real-life G.I. Joe.
美国90年代动画，讲述反恐部队和恐怖组织对抗的故事
但是很明显他和权威不能相溶
But he's got a bit of an issue with authority.
真是漂亮的侦查工作 孩子
That's a mighty fine detective job you've done, son.
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir.
但是 做起来可没有你说说那么容易
But... it ain't as easy as all that.
所以你知道Oodie兄弟么
So you do know the Oodie Brothers?
我说过 我全知道
Like I said, I know all.
我不能把男孩们带过来
I can't just bring them boys
仅仅因为某个费城来的制服男想要我这么做
in 'cause some suit from Philadelphia wants me to.
嗯 如果某个从芝加哥来的制服男要求你
Well, you can if some suit
你就会这么做了吧
from Chicago tells you to.
你呆在这里的时间越长 你就越会明白
The longer you stay down here, the more you're going to realise,
我们不喜欢被要求要做什么 孩子
we don't like being told what to do, son.
现在...
Now...
... 如果你不介意
...if you'll excuse me,
我还有其他工作要处理
I got other work to attend to.
不 Sheriff  听着 我只是想要些
No, Sheriff. Listen, I'm just asking for,
你懂的 一个小小的合作
you know, a little cooperation.
一旦这个事情告一段落 我就不再缠着你了
Once this thing gets wrapped up, I'll get out of your hair.
你为什么就不能让我把心思放在我的小镇呢
Why don't you let me worry about my county?
午夜的时候我们能到Dallas
We'll be in Dallas by midnight.
我可以开到开不下去为止
I'll drive us until I can't drive no more.
你能想象她就这么走向前
Can you believe she went ahead
然后预付了我5000块么
and paid us five grand up front?
我知道 不是么
I know, right?
我是说
I mean,
你会认为她有一些信任方面的问题 对吧
you'd think she'd have some trust issues, right?
嘿 是他们中的每一个人
But hey, each to their own.
他们中的每一个人都有 伙计
Each to their own, man.
他们中的每一个人
Each to their own.
现在 我知道我们有到Austin的地址
Now, I know we've got an address to Austin,
但是难道她不应该给我们
but shouldn't she have given
那个孩子的画像或者别的什么吗
us like a picture of the kid or something?
你以为那里能有几个孩子
How many kids you reckon they got up there?
我的意思是 他们不是在开日托中心
I mean, they ain't running a day-care centre.
- 好的   - 是啊
- OK. - Yeah.
如果我们到那了以后发现Rob是个婴儿呢
What if we get there and Rob's a baby?
呃 如果他是婴儿 他们就会留下婴儿的垃圾
Well, if he's a baby, they got baby junk up there.
哦 那很有才
Oh, that's smart.
我是说 他们不可能
I mean, it's not like they're riding around
带着个放在鞋盒子里的婴儿跑了
with a baby in a shoebox or nothing.
我是说 拜托
I mean, come on.
除了那个 留在
Besides that, the bullet
Celeste肚子上的子弹的痕迹
scars didn't look too fresh
看起来也不太新鲜了
on Celeste's belly.
- 你说的对  你说得对   - 是啊
- You're right. You're right. - Yeah.
如果不止一个孩子呢
What if there's more than one kid?
你干嘛问我这么多
Why are you asking me so many
该死的问题 伙计 我们能不谈这个了吗
goddamn questions, man? We just went over this! What?
你想知道什么  你到底想知道什么
What do you want to know?! What do you want to know?!
我们怎么知道哪个是Rob
How will we know which is Rob?
我会去问哪个是Rob
I'm gonna say which one's Rob!
这个怎么样 我会说
How about that? I'm gonna say,
"你知道什么 我不想要Kevin
"You know what, I don't want Kevin!
我不想要Michael
I don't want Michael!
不 我不想要Stephen"
No, I don't want Stephen!"
如果周围有
If there's a bunch of
一堆该死的孩子 我就会说 我想要Rob
fucking kids around I'm gonna say, "I want Rob!
怎么样 他妈的 伙计
How about that? Fucking hell, man!
这是一个该死的简单的入侵和掠夺
It's a damn simple smash and grab!
谁在我们面前我们就弄死谁 然后带走Rob
We smash whoever's in front of us and we take Rob!
该死的 简单又清晰
Damn! Plain and simple!
什么  抱歉 Lincoln
What? Sorry, Lincoln.
我不知道你为什么鬼叫鬼叫的
I don't know why you have to yell...
我的娘娘腔兄弟是不会闭嘴的
Your faggoty brother won't shut up!
我很好奇 你知道的
I'm inquisitive, and you know that!
你从哪儿学到这个词的 好奇?
Where'd you learn that word? Inquisitive?
你他妈从哪儿学来的
Where the fuck did you pick that up?
就在我的字典里 伙计
It's in my lexicon, man!
- 蠢货 对么   - 它就在我的脑海里
- Jackass. Yeah? - I've got it up here.
你们不了解我的地方可多了
There's a lot you don't know about me.
你准备好方便的时间了吗
Are you ready for a potty break?
你又读过多少书 操他妈的
How many books you read, motherfucker?
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
我们在Crockett
We're in Crockett.
Davy Crockett  几点了
Davy Crockett. What time is it?
4点了
Four.
嘿
Hey.
额... 我猜每个皮纳塔里都有一个小糖果
Hm... I guess there's a little candy in every pinata.
有免费的呦
Got some free shit!
放轻松 Van Damme  嘿
Take it easy, Van Damme! Hey.
Hadji在前台说
Hadji at the front desk said
我们离Austin只有几个小时的距离
we're only a few hours from Austin.
很好
Nice!
- 谁   - 该死  你觉得还有谁
- Who that? - Fuck. Who do you think?
别接电话 伙计
Don't answer that shit, man!
别接 你怎么...
Don't answer it. Don't you...
- 嘿   - 嘿?
- Hey. - Hey?
别跟我打招呼  你在哪里
Don't hey me. The hell are you?
德克萨斯
Texas.
德克萨斯?
Texas?
你他妈怎么
Well, what in the Sam
会在德克萨斯呢
Hill could you possibly have to do in Texas?
嘿 伙计 看看这个
Hey, man. Check this out.
胜利之光里的二叠纪体育场
Permian Stadium from Friday Night Lights.
热血体育连续剧
就在这途中
It's on the way!
我有份工作要到这儿
I took a job out here.
哦 你找到工作了 好吧 原谅我
Oh, you took a job! Well, excuse me.
我之前在想什么 我忘了
What was I thinking? I forgot
你们是自由职业的艺术家
you guys are freelance artists.
所以 Brick先生
So, Mr Brick,
你的工作是什么
what job did you take?
嘿 没什么大不了的 伙计
Look, it's not a big deal, man.
好吧 这只是一个小菜一碟 我们可以处理的
All right? It's just a little gig out here. We can handle it.
噢 你要处理它就像你昨天处理我一样么
Oh, you're going to handle it like you handled me yesterday?
你们没能检查一次
It's bad enough
那个该死的地址已经够糟的了
you can't check a damn address,
你们居然还把那些猪肉搁在我的后院里?
but you also got to lay them pork chops out in my backyard?
- 计在我们的账上好了   - 那是什么
- Put it on our tab. - What was that?
- 没什么   - 注意你说的话 孩子
- Nothing! - You watch your mouth, son.
这不是开玩笑
This ain't a joke.
这个小过失对我来说将会很痛苦
This little misstep is gonna be a pain for me,
但是对你来说
but you
你可能已经他妈的捅了马蜂窝了
may have just stuck your dick in a hornet's nest.
你在说什么 你什么意思
What are you talking about? What do you mean?
有一个ATF的探员找上我了
I've got some jackleg ATF agent up my ass,
指望找个罪名把你们关起来
looking to make a name for locking up you idiots.
我最不希望看到的就是
The last thing I need is for
你们这群白痴又在引起不必要的注意
you dumb shits to draw more unneeded attention.
我认真的 Brick 我最好
I mean it, Brick. I better
不要听到你在德克萨斯那个白痴工作的事
not hear shit about your little Texas job.
保持你的屁股不要触电
Keep your ass off the grid.
不要打我家里的电话  把这个号码记下来
Don't call my house. Write this number down.
而且看在上帝的份上 丢掉那该死的手机
And for the love of God, get rid of that damn cell phone.
- 是的 先生   - 最好这样
- Yes, sir. - Damn well better.
你浪费的时间就是我的退休金 那是你的屁事
You mess around and fuck up my pension, that's your ass.
我又不认识你
I don't even know you.
嘿
Hey!
看这个 伙计  二叠纪体育场
Check it out, man! Permian Stadium!
就在这途中 伙计
It's on the way, man!
你想要赢 就让好兄弟去
You want to win, put bubba in!
不再这途中 笨蛋
It's not on the way, jackass.
就在 伙计 在德克赛斯州的奥德萨市
It is, man! It's Odessa, Texas!
嗯哼
Huh?
伙计 别因为你被骂了就把气出在我身上
Man! Don't take it out on me because you got your ass chewed.
我们有活干了 男孩子们
We got work to do, boys.
我会得到我的徽章
I'll get my badge.
不 我想我们会去坐老罗斯福监狱的
No. I figured we'd do the old Roosevelt slammer.
该死的 是啊
Fuck, yeah!
被我得手了 贱人
Dibs, bitch!
Montane 该死的 我没有
Goddamn it, Montane! I didn't
想让你把那地方给炸了
want you to blow the place to hell and back.
我他妈一分钱也不会给
I don't give a shit!
你他妈的能不能认真听我说
Would you fucking listen to me every now and then?
拜托 该死的 过来宝贝 过来
Please? Goddamn it. Come here, baby. Come here!
我不知道你妈妈跟你说了什么
I don't know if your mama told you,
但是你穿得更性感了
but you are hotter than shit.
该死的
Goddamn.
他妈的 这他妈是堆狗屎 伙计们
Fuck. That's the shit right there, boys!
从现在开始 别在研究鸡毛蒜皮的小事了
From now on, no more nickel and diming!
你懂了么 只要最好的
You get it? Only the finest!
嘿 她怎么没有赤裸着
Hey, how come she's not naked?
不知道 老板
Don't know, boss.
去查出来
Find out.
嘿 我需要你的时候我会打电话给你的
Hey. I'll call you when I need you.
好的 拜
All right. Bye.
就没有人知道如何使用策略了么
Doesn't anybody know how to use finesse any more?
你还好么
You all right?
头盔他妈的不太适合
The helmet ain't work for shit.
我告诉过你了  啊哈
I told you. Aah!
好的 你往东走 我往西走
All right, you go east, I go west!
清晰简单  强行夺取
Plain and simple. Smash and grab.
哦 该死的
Oh, shit.
我的错 女士 你还好吧
My bad, lady. You OK?
为我辩护下 这都是因为你为一个混蛋工作
In my defence, you do work for an asshole.
你是Rob吗
You Rob?
Brick!
上帝啊 Brick
Goddang. Brick!
该死的
Goddamn it.
他妈的
Fuck.
哦 操
Oh, shit.
老板 老板 你没事吧
Boss! Boss, are you all right?
它他妈的看起来像什么 Marty
What the fuck does it look like, Marty?
他妈的看起来像炸弹爆炸
It looks like a fucking bomb went off.
Denny?
- 到底发生了什么   - 那个孩子
- What the hell happened? - The kid.
- 说什么   - 三个家伙进来
- Say what? - Three guys come in.
是的 我知道有三个人进来
Yes, I know three guys came in!
他们他妈的一路闯进来
They came all the fucking way in!
- 我看到了   - 他们带走了那个孩子
- I see that! - They took the kid.
操 该死的
Fuck! Goddamn it!
他们射杀了我该死的女仆
They shot my motherfucking maid!
好的 Marty 我知道已经过去一年了
OK, Marty, I know it's over a year ago,
但是我需要你想想 好吗
but I need you to fucking think, OK?
你确实杀了Celeste 对不对
You did kill Celeste, right?
你不会骗我吧 你会吗
You wouldn't lie to me about that shit, would you?
我把三颗子弹射入了她的内脏
I put three bullets in her gut.
她看起来死了
She looked dead to me.
但是你没检查她是否真的死了 你没有吧
But you didn't check to see if she was dead, did you?
应该是没有
Guess not.
那可是我们的金票啊 我操你妈
That was our golden ticket, you stinking fuck!
我该怎么付清这个 你有钱么
How am I going to pay for this? You got the dough?
你的肥屁股里他妈的有存钱罐吗
You got a fucking piggy bank in your fat ass?
对不起 老板
Sorry, boss.
好的 只要你抱歉
OK. As long as you're sorry,
我想这才是重要的 不是吗
I guess that's all that matters, isn't it?
我会处理的 老板
I'll take care of it, boss.
我去确定  我去处理
I'll make sure it's right. I'll take care of it.
好 好 谢谢 谢了
Good, good. Thanks, thanks.
是啊  去拿我该死的药 你会么
Yeah. Hand me my goddamn pills, will you?
你还想去看看那辆车吗
You still want to go look at that car?
那个Carlos让你变残废了?
That Carlos man make you cripple?
嗨 伙计
Hi, buddy.
我不认为他能说话
I don't think he can talk.
- 嗯 不会这么惨吧 伙计   - 什么
- Well, ain't this some shit, man. - What?
他整个都 你知道...
That he's all, you know...
- 别那么做   - 什么
- Don't do that shit! - What?
因为你太刻薄了 他不会受得了的
'Cause you're being mean! He can't help it.
你还好吧
You OK?
你受伤了吗
You hurt?
你没事吧  他能听的懂我们
You OK? He can understand us.
你是怎么明白他的意思是"我很好"的?
How the hell did you get "I'm OK" From that?
嘿 听着 伙计  我们不会伤害你
Hey, look, buddy. We ain't going to hurt you,
好么 Celeste让我们来的
all right? Celeste sent us.
你知道Celeste吗
You know Celeste?
是啊 他动了 看到没 他听得懂我们的
Yeah! There he goes! See? He understands us just fine.
再说一次 你怎么知道他的意思是什么
Once again, how the hell do you know what he's saying?
你是温情大姐姐吗
You the tard whisperer?
你再说一遍 我就杀了你
You say that again, I'm gonna kill you.
我没在戏弄他 我就是说说
I'm not making fun. I'm just saying.
再说一遍 你就是在戏弄他
Say it again. You are making fun.
我真没在戏弄他 我只是说说的
I'm not making fun. I'm just saying.
你就在戏弄他
You are making fun of him.
只是有点奇怪
It's just a little weird
她没有提到这个可怜的小伙子
that she didn't mention the poor little fella's
已经残废了 你知道么
all buggered up, you know?
它不重要
It don't matter.
她让我们来带走Rob
She sent us to get Rob.
我们已经带走Rob了
We got Rob.
好吗
All right?
伙计 你还好吧
You good, buddy?
我不是在说风凉话
I wasn't being mean.
你就是在说风凉话
You were being mean!
你把他当做笑柄
You were making fun of him.
上帝保佑  他没法控制这些
Bless his heart. He ain't got no control over that.
他不在客厅里真他妈太好了
It's a damn good thing he wasn't in the living room.
我只是随便说说
I'm just saying.
嗯 我们可以那么做
Yeah, we can do that.
哦 我们能做到的
Oh, we can get that done.
好的 Carlos
All right, Carlos.
我只是还要完成一点小事
I'm just finishing up a little something here.
然后我们就上路
Then we'll get on the road.
你难道不担心么 甜心
Don't you worry about a thing, sweetie.
抱歉 议员
Excuse me, councilman.
什么 他想要洗澡
What? He wanted a bath.
另一个准备好了么? 我都没脱光呢
Another one already? I didn't even get off.
为了Carlos
It's for Carlos.
嗯 这就好多了
Well, that makes it a bit better.
不会有比这感觉更好的了 Bill
Doesn't get much better than this, Bill.
要是鱼能像这些恙螨一样
It'd be better than this if
赶紧咬钩的话就好了
the fish was biting as well as these chiggers.
你要害到我了
You gotta be shitting me.
这就是真正的警察事要处理的事情吗
This is where the real police matters are handled, huh?
哦 你是说动用私人财产?
Oh, you mean on private property?
是啊 有些时候是要
Yeah, sometimes it is.
我是Anthony Reese 是ATF特工
Anthony Reese, ATF.
Bill Hawkins 很高兴见到你
Bill Hawkins. Nice to meet you.
Bill是一名州议员
Bill's a representative for the state.
啊 很高兴见到你 先生
Ah, nice to meet you, sir.
Bill 你听说过
Bill, have you heard about
在我们这里有个正在进行的调查吗
an investigation going on in our area?
不 我没有听说过
No, I haven't.
看来Reese探员
It seems Agent Reese
是上面派来检查我们的工作的
was sent down here to check up on us.
鉴于他是常青藤盟校毕业的
Seeing as he's an Ivy League grad,
我想 这让他比我们更胜任这份工作
I guess that makes him better at our jobs than we are.
哦 是吗
Oh, is he now?
别这么说 我无意插手你们的工作
No. I'm not trying to intrude,
只是想从旁协助
only assist.
警长 我觉得我们一开始就把关系搞砸了
Sheriff, I feel like we got off on the wrong foot.
我们是一个阵营的 我不想让你觉得
We're on the same team. I don't want it to feel like
我侵犯你的地盘 我只是...
I'm infringing on your territory. I just...
我真的觉得那三兄弟跟案情有关
I really think we have something with these Oodies.
我们钓鱼的时候不谈工作的事儿 伙计
We don't talk business when I'm fishing, son.
我要抛鱼钩啦 当心鱼钩
When I'm about to cast. Don't get hooked!
当然
We can, however,
明天在我办公室 我们可以谈论所有事情
talk all about it tomorrow at my office.
看到你们北方佬来到这儿 仗着当局的权威
It don't excite me that some Yankee's come down here
在我好朋友面前作威作福
imposing his authority
可让我高兴不起来啊
on one of my best friends.
上次我查的时候
This county has the lowest
整个州我们这个县的犯罪率是最低的
crime rate in the state, last time I checked.
- 就是   - 我知道你们民主党
- Uh-huh. - I know you Democrats
认为我们需要你们的帮助
think we need your help,
但你听好了 我们不需要
but I'm here to tell you that we don't.
要在哥伦比亚特区跟你对抗 我可真够倒霉
Bad enough I've gotta fight you in D.C.
现在你可以
Now you can just ease your
像你进来那样 从这儿出去
way out of here the same way you eased in.
好让我享受剩下的午后时光
I'd like to enjoy what's left of my afternoon.
那...好吧
Alrighty, then.
你为什么不回家 去你老婆身边待着呢
Why don't you go back home to that wife of yours?
她一个人抚养孩子多辛苦啊
It must be hard raising a baby all by herself.
你的俱乐部真不错
Pretty classy joint you've got here
谢谢 你的衬衫不错
Thanks. Nice shirt.
- 你就是Lucky   - 是的
- You Lucky? - That's right.
我们看看那个
Let's see about that.
嘿 家伙 帮我把后面那该死的关掉好吗
Hey, man, why don't you turn that shit off back there for me?
那是Mac
That's Mac.
他98岁高龄
He's 98 years old.
我觉得他有权利看一些色情的东西
I think he's earned the right
如果他想的话
to watch a little T and A if he wants.
是吗 可他一动不动的
Why? He ain't jerking nothing.
呃 是这样 但是自从
Yeah, well, he's been
我开创这家俱乐部以来
watching that stuff
他就一直在看那些玩意儿
since I opened the joint,
所以我就让他看咯 这没问题吧
so I'm gonna keep it that way, all right?
哦 那这样吧
Well, how about this?
我过去那儿
If I go back there, I'm
我就弄死Mac 打碎你的电视 怎样
gonna bust up Mac and your TV. How about that?
呃 你不是开玩笑的吧
Yeah, is that a fact?
怎么回事儿
What the fuck?
看到了吗 我这儿有个未成年呢
See, I got a minor with me.
我可不希望他听到那些东西
I'd appreciate it if he wouldn't have to listen to that.
嘿 Mac 我要把电视关了 好吧
Hey, Mac, I'm gonna give it a rest for a second, all right?
我来找一个朋友 Terry
I'm looking for a friend of mine. Terry.
Macky
Macky?
我要关了电视
I'm gonna give it a rest!
Mac
Mac.
说话啊 Mac Mac
Say, Mac. Mac?
看来Mac终于看够了
It looks like Mac finally had enough.
嘿 伙计
Hey, man.
让我猜猜 这就是你说你会回来的部分
Let me guess. This is the part where you say
我说的对吗
you'll be back. Am I right?
我会回来的
I'll be back.
你看过这个电影吗
You know this movie?
我会回来的
I'll be back.
哦 你是不是觉得很神奇啊
Well, ain't you full of surprises?
嘿 我是Lucky 嗯
Hey, this is Lucky. Yeah,
听着 帮我叫辆救护车过来 好吗
listen, I need an ambulance down here, OK?
Mac好像过世了 好吧
It seems like Mac's passed on, OK?
你这儿除了酒吧小吃 没有别的吃的了吗
You got anything to eat back there besides the bar food bullshit?
我得去拿
I have to go get it.
好的 搞点好吃的 伙计
Well, rustle something up, man.
给这孩子弄点东西吃
I need something for the kid,
快点儿 我们赶时间呢 如果你不介意的话
please. We're in a big hurry if you don't mind.
哦 是吗 你们在逃难吗
Oh, yeah? You running from something?
该死
Goddamn.
你们好啊 美女们 要点什么喝的吗
How's it going, ladies? Need something to drink?
还不知道想喝什么呢
Don't know what we'd like yet.
没问题 想到了就告诉我们
All right. Well, you let us know when you do.
你们可真养眼啊
Looking real good up in here.
帮我拿着
Watch this.
我先来
Dibs.
我是McQueen
Name's McQueen.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
可以为你买杯饮料吗
Can I buy you a drink?
她叫Jez 你可以给我们买杯饮料吗
Her name is Jez. And you can buy us a drink.
Lucky 给我的新朋友Jez
Lucky? Can I get us some beers
还有她的女伴们
for my new friend Jez.
来几瓶啤酒好吗 另外 那孩子的还在等吃的
And her ladies. And that kid's still waiting on his food.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
自己想办法
Figure it out.
说说你的故事 我会假装在认真听的
What's your story? And I'm gonna pretend I'm listening.
狗娘养的 说什么不想让那孩子看色情片
Damn bullshit! Don't want the kid seeing porn,
但是那些小妖精一进来
but when some sweet tail walks in,
他们却忘得一干二净了 不是吗
they forget all about that, right?
四年来头一次有几个长相甜美
First time in four years I got some sweet,
清新可爱的女人进来这儿
fresh snapper come in here,
我却在这儿
and I'm down here making
给那帮公路武士们做他妈的三文治
fucking sandwiches for the Road Warriors?
去他娘的
Kiss my fucking ass!
嗯...
Hm...
想跳舞吗
Wanna dance?
正是时候
About damn time.
不是那样
Not like that.
嗯...
Um...
也不是那样跳
Not like that either.
Brick?
那是个骗子还是同性恋的名字?
Is that the Big Whopper or the Ponytail?
对了 Marty跟你问好
By the way, Marty says hi.
是吗 那你告诉Marty "去你妈的
Yeah? Well, tell Marty, "Fuck you.
我看你怎么躲过下一颗子弹
" I see you dodged another bullet.
你怎么知道我电话号码的
How'd you get this number?
宝贝 现在我想要的东西 就没有得不到的
These days, baby, I can get just about anything I want to.
比如 现在我要开车去拿回我的钱
For instance, right now I'm getting back my paycheque on wheels
从你派出的那堆业余人员手里
from those amateurs you sent.
你个爱财如命的混蛋
Moneygrubbing piece of shit!
我们怎么了 宝贝
What happened to us, baby?
我们之前很甜蜜 不是吗
We were good once, weren't we?
去你的 我们从来没有甜蜜过
Fuck you! We were never good.
我被你耍了
I got played and that's that.
喔 等等
Whoa. Hang on a second.
要是真有谁被耍了 那个人是我
Anybody got played, it was me.
被你这个婊子耍了
I thought I had a bitch that was down with this shit.
你杀了他父母 你个神经病
You killed his parents, you psycho!
还是我带你介入他们的生活的 想想就恶心
And it makes me sick that I brought you into their world!
你不觉得是因为他们看人的眼光太差么
Don't you think they're just a bad judge of character?
这又不是我的错 谁让你的朋友太有钱了
It ain't my fault all your friends are richer than shit.
难道你一点也不知道么
And you know something?
想来想去 我觉得你是知道的
At the end of the day, I think you knew.
如果我知道 我会
If I knew, I would have
在你睡觉的时候烧死你这个窝囊废
lit your gutless ass on fire while you slept!
现在的你 才是我认识的那个易怒的婊子
Now, there's the feisty bitch I know!
我真心希望事情的结果不是这样
I wish it hadn't ended up the way it did.
但是Clyde会怎么做呢
But what's Clyde gonna do
如果Bonnie发起狂来惹他生气
if Bonnie crosses him and goes soft?
再说了 那个狗娘养的要钱干嘛
And besides, what does that son of a bitch need money for?
我是说 一个轮椅能要多少钱
I mean, how much can a wheelchair cost?
两三百美元吗
Two or three hundred dollars?
你个没良心的混账东西
You lost, motherfucker!
我会把Rob带回来的
Rob's coming back with me.
你看着办吧
Deal with it.
哦 小妞
Now, girlie,
看来你经历一次之后还没学乖
obviously you didn't learn the first time around.
我来告诉你这事儿会怎么结束
Let me tell you how this shit's gonna end.
我派了一些可怕的女人去解决这件事
I sent some really awful bitches to handle this situation.
现在 一旦她们找到你的同伙
Now, once they track down your fellas,
不会是一场血腥屠杀
it's not gonna be a bloodbath.
而是一场性感表演
It's gonna get fucking sexy.
把他们一个个 分散开来
They'll single them out, divide them up, then thin the herd.
每个人都会忘乎所以
Each one will have forgotten about everything,
只能看到眼前挑逗他们的陌生女郎
except for the fine piece of strange grinding on them.
然后 毫无预兆 他们就死翘翘了
Then, without warning, their lives will be snuffed out
最后那些女人会把Rob送过来
and the girls deliver Rob just
我刚好能为他的18岁生日做好准备
in time for me to plan the boy's 18th birthday.
你本应该老老实实待着的 亲爱的
You should have stayed dead, darling.
因为 除非你的名字是耶稣
'Cause unless your name is Jesus,
否则根本没必要重返人世
you had no business coming back.
回见
See you soon.
怎么不试试我的厉害
Why don't you try a taste of me?
哦 你们好啊 大家伙
Well, hi, big guy.
尝尝我的长枪
Here's my boom stick.
哦 他妈的
Oh, shit!
嘿 嘿 别在上面乱搞
Hey! Hey, don't be fucking around up there!
操
Fuck!
哦 刚才那些妞是我交往时间最长的女人了
Well, those girls were the longest relationship I ever had.
你没事吧 伙计
You OK, bud? Huh?
好了 我们得走了 快点
All right, come on. I wanna move. Let's go.
在这鬼地方Lucky要走运咯
Lucky's about to get lucky up in this motherfucker.
我要好好享受 整晚享受
Do this shit right. I'm gonna do it all night.
我可是花了钱的
I've got to pay to play.
五个如花似玉的美人儿来到这儿
Five girls like that come in there,
你就得花钱
you've got to pay to play.
那些猫咪们可不是免费的
That pussy ain't free.
你别笑 你得帮我
Don't you laugh at me. I'm gonna make you work all this,
帮我减减肥
all this extra weight off me,
因为我整天在这
because all I've been doing
就是吃炸鸡 亲爱的 还有炸甘蓝
is eating fried chicken, baby and fried collards!
油炸的 全部都是油炸的
Fried! Everything fried!
我昨天看到一个人在做油炸甜糕
I saw a man fry a Twinkie yesterday.
希尔县政府仍在通缉这些画像上的歹徒
Hill County officials have these renderings to go on.
宝贝 一会再打给你
Baby, let me call you right back.
歹徒挟持了一个未成年人同行
...the assailants are travelling with a minor,
情况非常危险 如果你看到任何
and appear to be highly dangerous. If you see anyone
特征相符的嫌疑犯
fitting this description,
请跟当地政府联系
please contact the local authorities.
就让我当个混蛋吧
I'll be a motherfucker.
下面请收看天气预报 Bob
Back to you with the weather, Bob.
那个性感的小妖精在我背上折断了她的高跟鞋
That sexy bitch broke her damn heel off in my back.
喔
Whoo!
刚才是怎么回事
What in the hell was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
打赌我会打电话给Celeste问清楚的
But you can bet I'm gonna call Celeste and find out.
疗伤时间到
Rambo time.
你等会该不会报复我吧
Now, you ain't gonna get me back for this later?
向我保证
Promise me now.
因为我觉得这个应该会很痛
'Cause I've got a feeling this is gonna hurt.
他扛住了 伙计
He's taking it, man.
像Dragon一样承受一切
Take it like Drago!
电光守护神
Drago
Drago.
Drago! Drago!
耶 宝贝儿
Yeah, baby!
哦 她可把你伤得够狠
Man! She got you good! Whoo!
希尔县政府仍在通缉这些画像上的歹徒
Hill County officials have these renderings to go on.
目击者称
Eyewitness accounts say
歹徒们挟持了一个未成年人同行
the assailants are travelling with a minor
情况非常危险
and appear to be highly dangerous.
如果你看到
If you see anyone
特征相符的嫌疑犯 请
fitting this description, please...
操
Fuck me!
嘿
Hey!
那帮人挺厉害的 不是吗
They did a really good job, didn't they?
看上去就是他们
It looks just like them too.
你看
Look at that.
报纸上到处都是有关他们的新闻
It was all over the news.
警长 这是第一次证据
Sheriff, this is the first time that evidence
明晃晃地出现在我的门前
has literally been brought to my doorstep.
我们还找到了他们的住址
We were able to pick up an address for them, too.
我会在中午对那里进行搜查
I'll have a search and seizure here by noon.
哦 奇怪啊奇怪
And surprise, surprise!
那些歹徒们
It's located on a piece of residential land
居然住在你们县 警长
here in your county, Sheriff.
难以置信吧
Can you believe that?
你的计划听起来不错 伙计
That sounds like a hell of a plan, son.
有什么要我帮忙的么
What can I do to help?
哦 貌似这儿的
Well, I'm guessing half the
大部分路线在我GPS上都显示不出来
roads that get me there won't show up on my GPS.
所以 如果你能够
So if you could do me a
送我到歹徒的住处
favour and simply escort me to the property,
那就再好不过了
that would be fantastic.
噢 你是说埃尔顿那间又老又破的棚屋吗
Oh... You mean that old-ass condemned shack out on Euleton?
伙计 你没听说吗
Son, you didn't hear?
消防队长让那些志愿兵把它烧了 用来训练
Fire chief let the volunteers burn that up for training.
烧了用来训练
Burn it up for training.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 我记得是定在今天早上呢
Yeah, I think it was scheduled for early this morning.
真是那样吗
Is that right?
那么 我建议你最好阻止他们
Well, I suggest you better stop them.
我可以打电话给Walters长官问问情况
I could call Chief Walters,
不过我很确信
but I'm pretty sure ain't
那儿只剩下烟和灰尘了
nothing left out there but smoke and ash.
哦 我感到很抱歉
My! I'm really sorry about that.
刚刚听起来好像真有什么事儿呢
It really sounded like you had something there.
混蛋 我受够了你这样浪费我的时间
Motherfucker, I'm done with you wasting my time.
这可是你自找的
I don't ever remember asking for it.
你现在在做的这些 扮演老好人
This good-old-boy justice thing you got going on,
让垃圾去处理垃圾
letting the trash take out the trash, saving tax dollars
把生活在最底层的人排除在体制外来节省税收
by keeping the bottomfeeders out of the system
好让自己能够整天去钓鱼
so you can just go fishing all day,
要知道你是在玩火
that's a slippery slope you're playing on.
现在
It's gotten to the point
你不比那些垃圾好到哪儿去 警长
where you're no better than they are, Sheriff.
没错 我要是你 我就会格外当心
Yeah, I'd be careful if I was you.
哦 我会慎重考虑你的意见的
Well, I'll take that under advisement.
放屁
Shit.
起来
Wake up.
去给Rob弄些吃的
Go get Rob something to eat.
我去打电话给Celeste
I'm gonna call Celeste.
噢 找到一顶好帽子 伙计
Ooh... Found the mother lode, boy!
我会付钱的 别担心 真是的
I'm gonna pay for it. Don't worry. God.
要知道 伙计 当你在商店打开某样东西
You see, man, when you open up something in the store...
你就得付钱
...you have to pay for it.
我小的时候没人告诉我
No one taught me that when I was young.
我历经艰难才懂得这个道理
I learnt that one the hard way.
从警察那里
From the cops.
怎么了
What?
怎么了 伙计
What's wrong, man?
你只是那样扭动 我不知道啥意思
I don't know you mean by all that squirming.
帮帮我 伙计 你要什么 嗯 要什么
Help me out, bud. What you need, huh? What you need?
你要小便吗
You got to take a piss?
你饿啦 天 你当然是饿了
You're hungry. Goddamn, of course you're hungry!
给你弄点吃的吧 好的 我们走
Let's get you something to eat, eh? OK. Let's go.
天哪
Man!
每次和这小男孩说话都像在猜谜
It's like working out a riddle every time talking to this boy.
早上好 美女 那啥
Morning, sunshine! You know,
我不记得我们的交易里面
I don't remember crazy-ass
还包括了那些疯狂的小妖精
biker chicks being involved in our deal.
我也不记得我们的交易里
I don't remember leaving
要让Carlos活着 Rob没事吧
Carlos alive in the deal either. Is Rob all right?
操
Fuck!
嗯 他可能被吓得半死 不过他很好
Yeah, he's probably scared half to death, but he's fine.
让我跟他谈谈
Let me talk to him.
他在里面吃东西
He's inside getting something to eat
跟McQueen一起 另外 我们得谈谈
with McQueen. Besides, you and I got something to talk about.
好吧 昨晚究竟是怎么回事
All right? What the hell was that last night?
我跟你说过了 Carlos会
I told you, Carlos would
想尽办法把Rob弄回去
try to get Rob back
如果你不杀了他的话
if you didn't kill him.
你到底在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我们杀了那里的所有混蛋
We killed every motherfucker in that place.
很明显你没有 Brick
Well, evidently not, Brick!
好吧 像Carlos那样的家伙
All right. Why would a guy like Carlos, what would he want to do
对Rob那种情况的孩子会有什么企图
with a kid in Rob's condition?
Carlos杀了Rob的父母
Carlos killed Rob's parents,
而且还瞒着我
and then lied to me about it.
这些事难道不该早点告诉我么
That might have been something you wanted to mention.
好吧 听着 我很抱歉
All right, look. I'm sorry.
Rob满18岁的时候会有一笔信托基金
Rob has a trust that matures when he's 18,
和他一起
and as legal guardians,
被托付给法定监护人
we would get him and eventually the money.
你早就该告诉我这些了 操
That too might be something that you wanted to mention! Fuck!
Rob的信托基金下周就可以兑现了
Rob's trust matures next week and...
Carlos会不择手段的
Carlos will do anything to get it.
Brick 他现在只有你了
Brick, you're all he's got.
好吧  新的方案
All right. New plan.
你在半路跟我们碰头
You meet us halfway.
好吧 在哪
Fine. Where?
密西西比州维克斯堡的大河口野营地
Vicksburg, Mississippi. Big Bayou Campground.
我会尽快到的
I'll be there as soon as I can.
还有如果你敢再骗我
And if you lie to me again,
Carlos会是你这辈子担心的最后一件事
Carlos will be the least of your worries.
我已经杀了五个婊子
I already dropped five bitches.
杀第六个眼都不用眨
I won't hesitate to make it six.
你可能听过小热狗卷
Now, you may have heard of pig in a blanket,
但这货是烤小热狗
but this here is a pig in the sun.
你想要把头发搭在胸脯上吗
You want hair on your chest, now, don't you?
脱衣舞女喜欢这样
Strippers like it.
把餐纸递给我 哥们儿
Hand me a napkin, man.
你还好吗
You all right?
别担心
Hey. Don't worry.
别担心 哥们儿
Don't worry, man.
没有什么能伤害Lincoln的
Ain't nothing will hurt Lincoln.
他很好
He's OK.
...确认与乡下的德克萨斯酒吧
...believed to be responsible for the shooting
枪击案有关
in a rural Texas bar.
他们带着一位残障少年 并确定携带武器
They are travelling with a disabled young man and believed to be
且非常危险  如果您发现他们千万不要靠近
armed and dangerous. Do not approach these men if you see them.
有人想要一颗窃笑炸弹吗
Who wants a Snicker bomb, huh?
你以为你能用它拐骗小孩离开这吗
Think you can kidnap some kid and get away with it?
好吧 你要是会数数的话 五个杀手婊子
Yeah, well, I guess if you do the math, five whore assassins
还不如三个傻子和一个瘸子吧
can't trump three retards and a fucking cripple.
我是说 照我的估计
I mean, well, according to my calculations,
他们现在应该已经到你的地盘上了
they should be in your area someplace by now.
但这是你们的该干的活 不是吗
But that's not my fucking job to figure out, is it?
拦路抢劫不是你们老本行吗
I mean, isn't owning the road your goddamn job?
我就是这么想的  好吧
That's what I thought. OK.
我不管你怎么做
Anyway, I don't give a shit what you do.
把那小子带回来给我就对了
Just get my boy back.
对 搞定它
Yes! Get it done!
- 喂   - 我们搞得一团糟
- Yeah? - We're in a world of shit down here.
嗯 然后现在要连我牵扯进来么
Yeah, and now it's spilling over into mine.
听着 我们准备去密西西比州的维克斯堡
Listen, we're going to Vicksburg, Mississippi.
行吗
OK?
大河口野营地  我们准备
Big Bayou Campground. We could...
停 停 闭嘴
Stop. Stop! Shut up!
快他妈闭嘴  我知道的越少越好
Just shut the fuck up! The less I know, the better.
我教过你更聪明的办法吧
I taught you better than this!
我只是想
Look, I just thought that if,
你知道 如果我们可以跑进去 然后很快搞定
you know, we could run in and do a quick...
别  别想那些有的没有的
Don't do that! Don't get ideas!
只要照老子说的做就好
Just do what the fuck I say!
照我说的做 事情就一帆风顺 不是吗
Things ran smooth when we did that, didn't it?
我帮你擦屁股 你也得照看好我的
I cleaned up your shit, you took care of mine.
我本来能很快搞定这个
I could have handled this hotshot.
但现在却曝光了
But now this shit has gone public.
这得怪你们自己瞎干
There's repercussions to working for yourself.
现在你学到教训了吧
About time you learned that.
什么意思
Meaning what?
我可不管了 Brick  我得明哲保身
I got to cut ties, Brick. I cleaned up everything on my end
所以 从现在起你得靠自己了
So, what you do from now on rests solely on your shoulders.
如果你敢回来 我就不得不摆平你们了
If you come back here, I got no choice but to put you down.
我得保护我的家人
I got a family to protect.
我会确保告诉小伙子们我们又自由了
I'll be sure to let the boys know that we're on our own again.
再说吧 Sheriff
Talk to you later, Sheriff.
Brick  我们得走了
Brick! We gots to go!
我们要红了
We made the news!
Hood海盗们  走着
Hood Pirates! Mount up!
把这个给我
Give me that!
- 你给Millard打电话吗  - 嗯
- You call Millard?   - Yeah.
他怎么说
Well, what did he say?
现确定犯罪嫌疑人是
The suspects in question are believed to be
Brick Oodie和他的两兄弟
Brick Oodie and his two brothers...
没什么
Nothing.
他们来自亚拉巴马州蒙哥马利的阿特摩地区
They hail from the Atmore area, located in Montgomery, Alabama.
他们把你画得像个傻逼  瞧
They drew you to look like a fag. Look at that.
你他妈吃错药了吗 老兄
What the fuck you do that for, man?
操 你干嘛啊 老兄
What the fuck, man?
来啊  来啊
Come on! Come on, huh?
- 你是要怎样   - 来啊
- What are you do...? - Come on!
我才不会揍你呢 你这个废柴
I ain't gonna fucking hurt you, you little faggot!
- 住手 老兄   - 来啊 来这儿啊
- Stop, man! - Come on! Come here!
想怎样  你想怎样
Want some? You want some?
- 操   - 你吃错药了啊
- Fuck! - What the devil got into you?
我害死我们了
I fucked us.
你什么意思
How you mean?
呃 我说
Uh, let's see.
Millard不会再罩我们了
Millard won't have anything to do with us any more
因为他没法摆平
'cause he can't clean up
摩托女在酒吧大干后造成的后果
that mess with the biker chicks down at the bar.
所以现在我们不能回亚拉巴马了
So now we can't go back to 'Bama.
还有我们在奥斯丁撂倒的那些狗娘养的
And all of them son of bitches we mowed down in Austin?
猜猜看我们忘了哪一个
Guess what we missed.
Carlos
Carlos.
而且他也不会罢休的
And he ain't gonna stop neither.
他早就开始追着Celeste了
He's already tracked down Celeste.
所以现在我们得带他
So now we gotta get him
直到该死的维克斯堡 这样他们就能消失了
to fucking Vicksburg so they can disappear.
好吧
Well...
船到桥头自然直
This is getting better by the minute.
我喜欢那个小家伙 就像其他人一样
Now, I like that little fella just as much as anybody.
但跟我说说吧
But tell me something. Just
给我个理由为什么我们为什么不能抛下他不管
give me one reason why we shouldn't bail right now.
他们没得选择
They ain't got no other options.
切 我们也没得选择好吧
Hell, we ain't got no other options either.
我的意思是 你瞧我们
I mean, look at us.
我们甚至不能照顾好自己
We can't even take care of ourselves.
你有没有想过
Has it ever crossed your mind
或许没有我们 他能过得更好
that maybe he stands a better chance without us?
这不一样
It's just different.
怎么不一样了
How's this different?
就是不一样
It's just different!
怎么操蛋的不一样了
How the fuck is it different?
我有过一个哥哥
We had a brother...
在我记事之前就已经死了
...who passed away before you can even remember.
他的状况和Rob差不多
He was in the same situation Rob's in.
他状况糟透了 而且还得坐在轮椅上
He was all buggered up, and he was in a wheelchair.
老爸每天都揍他
Daddy beat his ass every single day.
把他当狗一样对待
Treated him like a dog.
而我却什么也做不了  有不一样吗
And there's nothing we could do about it. Different.
好吧 不提他了
Well, he gets a pass.
我不知道为什么你什么都没说
I don't understand why you didn't say nothing.
你怎么从来没跟我们说起过
How come you never said nothing?
你想要我怎么说
What do you want me to say to you?
对不起 行了吧
I'm sorry, all right?
但自从我见到这个小伙子开始
But ever since I've seen this fella,
我就止不住的想起这件事
I can't stop thinking about it.
他怎么死的
How'd he die?
不知道 他就在那 然后死了
I don't know. He was there one day and gone the next.
我问过老爸一次
I asked Daddy about it one time,
但他就当放屁一样什么也没听见
but that went over like a fart in church.
他叫什么
What was his name?
- 他们没给他起名字   - 我操
- They never named him. - Fuck me.
发现那几个狗杂种的了  就在前面
Got them bitches! Dead ahead!
这次 尽量别伤着那个小兔崽子
And this time, try not to hit the motherfucking baby.
他们来了
Here they come!
我给了所有她需要的
I'm giving it all she's got.
Monaco什么也没留下
Monaco ain't got nothing left!
绑紧Rob  他们来了 小伙子们
Strap in Rob! Here they come, boys!
我操这些狗杂种要干嘛
What the hell is this motherfucker?
嘿 Rottweiler
Hey, Rottweiler!
你最好退到后面去 傻逼
You better back the fuck up, mutt!
圣诞快乐 混蛋
Merry Christmas, motherfuckers.
那孩子在后座上
The kid's in the back!
他们把孩子带走了
They took the kid!
我说了叫你绑紧他的啊
I thought I told you to strap him in!
他们把门都给拉走了
They took the fucking door,
老兄 我现在真的觉得
Man! I really don't think a fucking seatbelt
重点不在安全带  快追啊
would have mattered right now! Go!
他怎么样了
Hey, he all right?
谁他妈知道啊
How in the fuck do I know?
他们追来了  就像你说的
Here they come! Just like you said!
来副驾驶座这边  你会感兴趣的
Hey! Help the driver. You want to see this.
看我们怎么操了你的保姆们
We're about to fuck your babysitters up.
- 来啊 小伙儿   - 来啊
- Come on, boy! - Whoo! Come on!
欢迎来到南部 狗杂种
Welcome to the South, motherfuckers!
怎么样啊 狗娘养的
Whoo! What you got now, bitches?!
没时间了 贱人
Time out, bitch!
不是吧  真是的  不要
No. No, indeed. Hell no.
想想办法啊 你是军师
Do something, you're the brains!
我们必须得想想办法
We've gotta figure something out!
什么
What?!
- 从顶上   - 从顶上
- Top rope! - Top rope!
狗日的
Motherfuckers!
干了他们 Lincoln  上啊
Get them, Lincoln! Come on!
快干了他们
Go get 'em!
他们减速了  他们减速了
They're slowing down! They're slowing down!
上
Come on.
Lincoln
Lincoln!
我们没事
We're good!
你还好吗 哥们
You all right, buddy?
你真是条汉子
You're one crazy redneck.
翅膀硬了是吗
Trying to be a tough guy? Huh?
想从我们眼皮底下开溜
Running away from us?
想来一根吗  你应得的
You want one of these? You've earned it.
Linc怎么样了
How's Linc?
不太乐观
Not so good.
什么
What?
你最好去看看他
You better check on him.
你看好Rob了
You got Rob?
操
Fuck.
都是你干的吗
You do all this?
老天爷干的
By God.
这可不是你的帽子 贱货
It ain't your hat, bitch.
干得好
Good work!
让我看看
Let me take a look.
来吧  让我看看
Come on. Let me see it.
靠
Shit!
不夸张地说
Well, I think it's safe to say that, uh,
这已经远远超过McQueen能处理的范围
that surpasses McQueen's level of doctoring.
- 我很好    - 你不好
- Fine.   - You are not fine.
我们得检查检查
We need to get that looked at.
我很好
Fine.
好吧  你很好
All right. You're fine.
好个屁
Fine, my ass.
操
Fuck!
McQueen
McQueen!
Montane  你他妈死哪去了
Montane! Montane, where the fuck are you?
狗屎
Shit.
操你妈
Goddamn it!
嘿 要搭你们一程吗
Hey. You guys need a ride?
他妈的这些人搞什么鬼
Who are these fucking people?!
不用了 老兄 我们很好  走吧
Nah, man. We're good. Just keep going.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
他制造了这些怪物
He practically made these monsters,
然后把他们晾出来
then hung them out to dry.
你玩儿我是吧
You gotta be kidding me.
他们为什么没在为老子工作
And why aren't they working for me?!
快进到车里  我是个护士  我能帮上忙
Just get in the car. I'm a nurse. I can help.
这个主意不错
That ain't such a bad idea.
找到了
Bingo.
发生什么事了
What happened here?
那个是我干的
I did that.
你指刺伤还是缝合
The stabbing or the stitches?
缝合
The stitches.
伤口已经感染了
Infection is setting in.
我淋了威士忌在上面
I poured whiskey on it.
我猜你是在电影里学的吧
Let me guess, you saw that in a movie?
是的  大部分
Yeah. Several.
Rob
Hey-Hey,Rob?
这由你来保管 好吗
You hold onto that, all right?
你知道这是他最珍视的东西
You know that's his prize possession.
等他好了他会需要的 好吗
He's gonna need it when he gets to feeling better, OK?
Chogan 我是Carlos
Chogan, this is Carlos.
这是我给你下的最后通牒
I'm only calling as a last damn resort.
有几个混蛋绑走了Rob 你给我去做了他们
Some asshole took Rob and I need you to kill him.
把那小子给我带回来 如果可能的话
If you can, bring me back the kid,
否则就把他们全做了
and if not, then fuck it.
如果我得不到他 别人也休想
If I can't have him, nobody can.
他们没走远
They're close.
走了
Finish up!
他会好起来吗
He gonna be all right?
我说过 这取决于你
Like I said, it's up to you.
你看起来很眼熟
You look really familiar.
- 是吗   - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
你住过廉价汽车旅馆吧
Do you stay in shitty motels?
我是打扫的
'Cause we clean them.
Crockett  我在那见过你
Crockett. That's where I've seen you.
这世界真小
Small world.
你为什么不去当护士呢
So why ain't you a nurse?
医院不雇用非法移民
Hospitals don't exactly hire illegals.
为什么不是合法的
Why don't you become legal?
你们国家的政策可没那么容易让我们合法
Your country doesn't make it that easy for us.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
只要到那填好文件就行了
Just go down to the place and fill out your paperwork.
告诉他们你想被法律认可就好了
Shit. Tell them you want to be legal.
我是说 你不是会英语吗
I mean, you speak the language.
在那每个人都说英语
That's more than most of them do out here.
你的无知真是难以置信
Your ignorance is unbelievable.
好吧 没错 我只是个无知的硬汉
Yeah, well, I might be just an ignorant redneck,
但至少我知道自己是什么样的人
but at least I know who I am.
我是说 你是护士
I mean, you're a nurse.
你就应该帮助别人
You ought to be helping people.
而不是刷马桶
Not scrubbing toilets.
这就是为什么你那么随心所欲吗
Well, is that why you do what you do?
因为你是这样的人
'Cause it's who you are?
我们就当是一家人在聊天吧
Let's just say it runs in the family. You know?
走上这一步你就别想有什么家人了
Well, you're not gonna have much family left at this pace.
听着 我真的很感激你为我们所做的一切
Listen, I really appreciate everything you've done for us.
我不能保证我能报答你 所以
I can't say that I'd exactly done the same thing, so...
不客气
You're welcome.
如果 如果我说付你两千美元
What would you say if... if I offered you two grand
送我们到密西西比州的维克斯堡 你怎么说
to get us to Vicksburg, Mississippi?
如果我要说服你别去做你将要去做的事呢
What do you say I convince you not to do what you're about to do?
我能带你去任何别的地方
I could take you anywhere else.
算了 我们必须去那里把事情解决 知道吗
Nah. This here's one of them kind of deals, you know?
我们生命里的大部分时间
We kind of had people
都由别人在掌控 你知道吗
controlling what we do our whole lives, you know?
是时候让我们自己来掌握命运了
It's time for us to take it by the reins.
照顾好那孩子
Please keep the kid safe for me.
不会再出事了
Nothing bad's gonna happen.
不过我们得先把事情做个了结
We've just got a job to finish.
我是外来的 但是我不傻啊
I'm foreign. I'm not stupid.
- 谢谢你   - 再见
- Thank you. - See ya.
再见
See you around.
我们还能用三千块钱填满个池塘吗
Can we still put a pool in with three grand?
你在想什么啊
What you thinking?
在想打地鼠游戏啊
I was thinking Whac-A-Mole.
以后就两个人的话 情况会有点棘手啊
But it's gonna be tough with just two of us.
什么叫就两个人了
What you mean two?
这个正好
That's fitting.
- 想不想我再推高点   - 不用了
- You want to go high?  - No.
去吧 你跑回家去
You go and run in the house.
不管听到什么
No matter what you hear,
也不管别人怎么说
no matter what the people say,
爸爸做的 只是在尽我所能
Papaw did what he could to
为你创造更好的生活  明白吗
make things better for you than he had. OK?
去吧  跑过去
Go. Run along.
派遣员说你在这儿
Dispatch told me you'd, uh... you'd be here.
是吗 我倒很想给你倒杯茶
Yeah. I'd offer you some sweet tea,
不过我习惯喝超浓的那种 都能杀死一头驴
but I like it stout enough to kill a mule.
你大概会接受不了
It might be too strong for you.
你猜在所有南方人的习惯和优点中
You know, of all the Southern idioms and charms,
我觉得哪个最有价值
you know which one I find the most helpful?
似火的热情吗
My extraordinary hospitality?
大家把什么东西都留着
The fact that nobody ever throws anything away.
警长 我得把这个给你
I've got to hand it to you, Sheriff.
没有任何资料显示
There was nothing in any
你跟他们有关系
database that ever connected you to them.
白天又没有收到电脑档案
Wasn't no computer files back in the day.
阿拉巴马州的却已经过时了
Another perk of Alabama being behind the times.
书面记录太容易弄丢了
Paper trail easy as hell to get rid of.
所以这只能代表一件事 负责的是个黄毛小子
Only thing this proves is that a young deputy was doing his job.
对对对 我就知道你会这么说
Right, right, right. Well, I figured you'd say that,
所以我仔细研究了
so I did a little further digging,
然后找到了这个
and I found this.
Henry 你漏掉了一些文件
You missed some paper, Henry.
05年5月26日 你签了1200美元账单
You signed for $1,200 dollars on May 26th, '05,
07年6月15日 800美元
$800 June 15th, '07
08年2月3日 1100美元
$1,100 on February 3rd, '08.
后面诸如此类
And it goes on and on and on.
那些钱是用来清理犯罪现场的
That money was issued for crime scene clean up.
我乐意雇谁做这事就雇谁
And I can hire anybody I damn well please.
是吗 案件还没发生
Well, since when do people
怎么就能清理现场了
get paid to clean up a crime before it happens?
警长 你确实是对的
You are right though, Sheriff.
你把犯罪率控制在全国最低
You've got the lowest crime rate in the state.
所以你也就不用给他们太多钱了吧
You certainly weren't paying them much though, were you?
难怪那些小崽子们都来找你
It's no wonder those dogs turned on you.
这样吧  这件事可以有两个结果
Now, listen. This story, you know, could end one of two ways.
要么 你帮我解决这事 跟我合作
You could either help me out, cooperate...
要么 我现在就逮捕你
...or I could just arrest you on the spot.
然后我自己把他们一网打尽
Take them down myself, eventually.
不管是哪个法子 我都得把你送进监狱
Look, either way, I've got to take you to prison,
但你要是表现良好
but you play nice,
你吃牢饭的日子就可以减少点
I'll see to it that your sentence is shortened.
搞不好你还会有机会
Maybe one day you'll be able to
看到你孙女从高中毕业呢
see your granddaughter graduate from high school.
我这可是出于职业的好意
Let's consider it a professional courtesy.
他们很快就会报复你的
They get big quick on you.
你迟早会知道的
You'll find that out sooner or later.
- 跟我来   - 别 别这样
- Come with me. - No, no, no. Come on.
- 这样可不好   - 你省省吧
- I don't think so. - Cut that shit out.
反抗是小孩子玩的把戏
Fighting's a young man's game.
- 那你要去哪里   - 维克斯堡
- Where are you going, huh? - Vicksburg.
这件事必须要我亲自了结
If anybody's gonna put an end to this, it's going to be me.
我才是有理由不相信你的人
You know, I'm the one that ain't supposed to be trusting you.
但是你赢了
Y'all won the damn war.
Lincoln以前摔跤的时候
Now this is the same face
就会在脸上画这个
paint that Lincoln used when he wrestled.
这样你跟我们就是一家人了
Solidifies you as one of us.
害怕吗
You scared?
现在你是Oodie家的一份子了
You're an Oodie now.
你得克服恐惧
You got to swallow that fear.
不过不管如何
For what it's worth,
你承受过太多 该得到更好的回报
I think you deserve more than what you've been through.
这不公平 就因为你不能自理
It ain't right, people taking advantage of you
他们都利用你
just because you can't help yourself.
我知道在你的一生当中
I know you may not have had a
可能不会出现多少值得尊敬的人
lot of people in your life you can look up to.
该死的 我不是要你尊敬我们
Hell, I ain't telling you to look up to us.
我只是想让你知道
I just want you to know that
我们会尽我们所能
we're going to do everything we can
护你周全
to keep you from getting hurt.
这个给你
I'm gonna leave you in charge.
这是我的新装备
My new lookout.
你已经有了很大进步
You've been promoted.
空的
Empty-
这不够
That ain't much.
形势所迫
It's gonna have to do.
Lincoln情况不大妙
Lincoln don't look so good.
谁说的 他好多了
Yeah, he's been better.
你觉得她会不会过来查看这件事
You think she's gonna come and see this thing through?
还是跑得远远的
Or is she just gonna run for the hills?
这个到时候我们就会知道了
I reckon we're about to find out, ain't we?
是啊
Yeah.
你觉得上帝为什么要创造他那样的人
Why you reckon God would make someone like him?
什么
What?
上帝为什么要让那么残忍的事发生在他身上
Why would God let something be wrong with him like that?
不知道  见鬼 我怎么会知道
I don't know. Hell, man, I don't know.
该死的 干嘛要问我这个
Hell, why you asking me that, man?
不知道  只是好奇
I don't know. Just been thinking about it.
我不好奇上帝为什么要创造他那样的人
I don't ask why God made men like him.
我好奇上帝为什么要创造我们这样的人
I wonder why he made men like us.
他们怎么样
How are the boys?
好吧
All right.
- 喂 Brick   - 怎么了
- Hey, Brick? - Hm?
我觉得我们当初应该把书念完的
I'm starting to think we should have finished school.
好歹我们也把初中念完了
At least junior high.
马上就会结束了
It's almost over, bud.
- 该死的   - McQueen
- Oh, shit! - McQueen!
操他妈的箭  该死的
A fucking arrow, man? Fuck!
快
Come on!
跑
Go!
跑啊
Move your ass, woman!
该死
Shit.
Brick Rob在哪里
Where's Rob, Brick?
他没事
He's safe!
在这儿别动
Stay right here.
我得去补充点儿弹药
I've gotta go get some ammo.
- 不行 我跟你一起去  - 你待在这儿
- No! I'm going with you.   - Stay here!
- 我要跟你一起去   - 操
- I'm going with you! - Fuck!
- 快啊   - 走
- Come on, man! - Go!
该死的 拿把枪
Grab a gun. Fuck.
快他妈带我去找Rob
Take me to fucking Rob!
你给我老实待在这儿
You're keeping your ass here!
有箭 我操
That was a fucking arrow, man!
Brick
Brick!
混蛋 这一点也不好玩  给我住手
Time out, motherfucker! This ain't fun no more! Stop!
该死的 见鬼
Fuck me! Oh, shit.
我他妈不是叫你待这儿的吗
I told you to fucking stay here!
不准说什么早告诉你了之类的话
You're really gonna say I told you so right now?
你管好你自己的事吧
You mind yourself, woman!
该死的
Shit!
我的天
God!
不准再动了
Don't fucking move!
出来吧 出来呀
Come out, come out.
你拿那个干嘛啊
What you gonna do with that, huh?
- McQueen   - 当心
- McQueen! - Hey!
John Redcorn 你今天走霉运了
You're about to have a bad day, John Redcorn.
现在是谁在走霉运啊
Remind me again who's gonna have a bad day?
真是稀奇
Ain't that a sight.
也就是说
So, uh...
你和你哥哥们绑架了这个孩子
you and your brothers kidnapped the kid from, uh...
这孩子是Martin女士的吧
...from Ms Martin, and
你们是不是打算借此索要赎金
you were planning on holding him for ransom?
是不是
Yeah? All right.
没错
That's what I said.
那其他的那些人呢 他们是什么人
And what about these other men here? Who are they? Huh?
- 啊   - 好吧 算了
- Oh... - All right. All right.
反正以后再监狱里
You'll have plenty of time
有的是时间思考答案
to think about your answers in prison. Yeah?
你是Reese特工吗
Agent Reese?
你是特工Simmons吧 幸会啊
Special Agent Simmons! Hey!
干得不错
Nice work.
谢谢夸奖 长官
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
你处理这片地方的动力让我深感佩服
I'm very impressed with how you navigated these waters.
所以我申请让你来管辖这片区域
I'm putting in a request to have you take over this territory.
不是吧 别 不要 不要啊长官
No, no, no, no, sir...
细节的地方别担心
Don't worry about the details.
我们会帮你处理好的
We'll get everything handled.
搬迁费等等 都会帮你处理好
Cover the moving expenses and everything.
但是我的妻子
But my wife...
这个地方很养人啊
It's a fine place to raise a family.
长官 我
Sir... I...
我敢保证 她一定会喜欢这里的
I'm sure she'll love it.
不是吧 我操
Oh... fuck me.
这下坑死了
Hey! Fuck me!
喂 老兄
Hey, bud!
我是来跟你说谢谢的
I just wanted to say thank you.
事情变成这样我很抱歉
I'm sorry it came down to all this.
没关系
Don't mention it.
只要把这小家伙照顾好就行了
Just make sure you take care of this little guy.
他可是很难缠的啊
He's one tough cuss.
我们没干掉那混蛋 对不起啊
Sorry we didn't get the fucker.
没关系的  Carlos难逃一劫
That's all right. Carlos will get his.
那个 老兄 我能不能跟他单独相处一会儿
Hey, man, you think I could have a minute?
我哪儿也不会去的
I ain't going nowhere.
好吧
All right.
别哪样
Hey, stop that.
要继承我们的优良传统哦
Make sure this shit didn't go down for nothing.
谢谢
Thank you.
哟 这不是那怪东西嘛
Well, ain't that some E.T. Shit?
你也知道Brick很别扭的 对吧
You know Brick's gay, right?
Rob 再见
See ya, Rob.
真是一波未平一波又起
The hits just keep on coming.
不过不管结果如何
No matter how this thing plays out...
我为你们感到骄傲
...I'm proud of you boys.
你不知道去的啊 见鬼
You busy? Goddamn it!
还有没有要我帮你做的了
Is there anything I can get you?
干什么
What?
有Carlos Lyman的包裹
I have a package for Carlos Lyman.
麻烦您签字
Please sign here.
鬼才要签字
I ain't signing shit.
包裹给我
Just give me the package.
你还好吧 先生
Are you all right, sir?
我好得很  不关你的事
Yeah, I'm fine. It's none of your goddamn business.
你得签字啊
You have to sign.
是不是很有意思
Isn't that great?
现在该死的邮递员
The fucking Postal Service
关系到我的安宁了
is concerned with my goddamn wellbeing.
这最好是一整盒现金
This better be a box full of fucking cash.
操你妈的
You bitch!